

Contacts

+38 050 755 69 18 werbolom@gmail.com Telegram LinkedIn GitHub

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- GIT
- WebPack
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Redux
- Node.jsNext.js

Soft skills

- Desire to constantly develop
- Quick learner
- Creativity
- Teamwork

Languages

- Ukrainian native
- English advanced
- Russian native

Oleksandr Melnychenko Full Stack Developer

Summary

I am an ambitious and young developer who strives for self-development and will not stop before any obstacles. For me, there is no ceiling that I can lean against and tell myself that I have learned enough. I have a lot of experience in communication with other people, as this is the key to successful teamwork. Analytical mindset has always helped me solve any problems both at work and in life. Solving problems has always been interesting and exciting for me and has always been one of my favorite activities.

Projects

1. Simply Chocolate | Link [HTML5, CSS3]

A website of a shop that sells chocolate. Role: developer. Responsibilities: Footer

2. Marvelous adventures | Link [JavaScript]

A web platform to look for Marvel heroes and comics. Role: developer.

Responsibilities: All functions of hero modal window

3. Money Guard | Link [React.js]

Online wallet that allows to save incomes and expenses. Role: developer.

Responsibilities: Dashboard table on HomeTab, bug fixing, preparing presentation of the project.

4. Power Pulse | Link [React.js, Node.js]

Application that helps people keep in good physical shape. Role: developer.

Responsibilities: profile page, bug fixing.

5. Ambidexter [Next.js, Tailwind]

Commercial project, website for online school of oratory and acting skills. Role: developer. Responsibilities: social media icons, contacts component, 'For whom' section, feedback form, ogp, project presentation

Work Experience

Frontend Developer at Rogo Practicum

Internship

April 2024 - Present

- Developing project according to design using React and Typescript
- Writing unit and integration test
- Reviewing my teammates' code
- Discussing inside team on best implemenation of features
- Working with GIT

Trainee at PBN Hill+Knowlton Strategies

September 2021 - February 2022

- Daily monitoring
- Translation of texts
- Surface research of the market
- Helped stop the blocking of the Ukrainian hero on Facebook

Analyst at ICM

August 2020 - February 2021

- Weekly monitoring of news
- Writing analytical note
- Searching for information in the Internet
- Prepared a well-known Ukrainian figure for an interview

Education

GOIT

Full-stack developer

March 2023 - September 2023

National University of 'Kyiv-Mohyla Academy'

Public Relations; Management in Healthcare

September 2020 - June 2022 | Master's degree

History and Archeology

September 2016 - June 2020 | Bachelor's degree